Oluwole Eesuola

Email Address: olueesuola@gmail.com
Phone Number: 2347068873539
Home Address: Lagos State, Nigeria

CAREER OBJECTIVE

A Technology adaptable and innovation-oriented Computer Administrator, Web developer and a graphics designer seeking a challenging career where knowledge and solution-oriented skills may significantly contribute to the organisation development and process. I have 5 years work experience in Web development and 3 years in IT support.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Signal ADoc Limited, Lagos

November 2022 – Till Date

Position Held: IT Support and Cloud Engineer.

Responsibilities

- ✓ Website, IOS and Android Testing (Manual Software Testing).
- ✓ Troubleshooting of Computers (User Support).
- ✓ Office 365 Administrator
- ✓ Cloud Server Administrator (GCP).
- ✓ Work in hand with the Frontend and Backend Team using DevOps practices and principles.

Micro Leasing Limited, Lagos

June 2021 – Oct 2022 (16 Months)

Position Held: IT Support and Web Developer

Responsibilities

- ✓ Installation of software for all departmental computers.
- ✓ Troubleshooting of Computers (User Support) and Printer Repairs.
- ✓ Core Banking Web App maintenance (Gemini and Bankone)
- ✓ Development of Web apps Visitors management system (Laravel) and Inventory (Laravel).
- ✓ Window Server Administrator.
- ✓ Card Access Control and Time Clocking System Maintenance and Monitoring.
- **✓** Monitoring of CCTV.
- ✓ Web development management and Graphic Designs.
- ✓ Networking (Intercom Connection, Switch, Routers, Hub, and cables clipping (RJ45 and RJ11)

IBILE Microfinance Bank Ltd, Ikeja, Lagos

June 2019 – May 2021 (23 Months) Position Held: Executive IT Officer

Responsibilities

- ✓ Installation of software for all departmental computers.
- ✓ Troubleshooting of Computers and Repairs.
- ✓ Core Banking maintenance (BankOne)
- ✓ Ensuring all apps for banking transactions (Core-Banking App, Mobile App, Loan App and USSD) are working perfectly well.
- **✓** Monitoring of CCTV.
- ✓ Weekly reports for the exco to be able to measure the bank progressing's.
- ✓ Web development management and Graphic Designs.
- ✓ Networking (Intercom Connection, Switch, Routers, Hub and cables clipping (RJ45 and RJ11))

DuKan George Limited, Ogombo, Ajah, Lagos

July 2018 – May 2019 (10 months) Position Held: Executive IT Officer

Responsibilities

- ✓ Developing websites and mobile apps for the company.
- ✓ In a team that developed a Rider solution App (Taxi mobile App) called CarXie (carxie.com), a Bill payment WebApp called Swift2pay (swift2pay.com) and Real Estate WebApp solution called VEGAHs (vegahs.com) a real estate management WebApp.
- ✓ Smoothing changes from old IT systems to new ones.
- **✓** Designing of flyers,handbills and graphics work when needed for the company.
- ✓ Agreeing on costs, timescale and standard to be met and monitoring of projects.
- ✓ Computer System Administrator (Troubleshooting, Software installs and Repairs.

Global sight services Limited, Akilo, Ogba, Lagos

April 2018 – July 2018 (3 months)

An Innovative company, employing creative minded people that can think out of the box, to explore that talent and to market the ideas to the entire world.

Position Held: Graduate Trainee (I.T department) Responsibilities

- ✓ Design Company website (globalsslng.com) and monitoring the website.
- ✓ Designing of project work websites, website portal built for artisan. (naijaquikfix.com).
- ✓ Designing of project work websites, website portal built for selling locally made goods. (wazobiamade.com).
- ✓ Designing of project work websites, website portal built for all professional drivers to store their information online. (nigeriadrivers.com).
- ✓ Designing of project work websites, website portal built for Innovative multi-concept limited. (innovationgroupng.com).

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

✓ B. Tech Computer Science, Ladoke Akintola University of Technology, Ogbomoso, Oyo state (2014).

ADDITIONAL CERTIFICATES OBTAINED

- ✓ Certification in Software Engineering, IVYARC, UK (2022).
- ✓ Web Master Training, GIIT (2022)
- ✓ Certificate on Digital Marketing (2018)
- ✓ National Youth Service corps (NYSC) Discharge Certificate (2017)
- ✓ Diploma in Web design (HTML & CSS), graphics design and Web development (PHP), HAYROYAL consults (June 2013).
- ✓ LAUTECH ICT Training Certificate (Upper Credits 2007).
- ✓ Certificate in Computer Engineering, Oyo City Computer (2005).

IT SKILLS

OPERATING SYSTEM	PROGRAMMING SKILLS	DATABASE
Windows, Linux.	HTML, CSS, PHP,	PhpMyAdmin, SQLite
	Bootstrap, JavaScript,	Postgresql.
IT SUPPORT SKILLS	React, NodeJS, Laravel &	
Window Server	WordPress.	OTHER IT SKILLS
Computer Repairs		CCTV Installation,
Printer Repairs	MICROSOFT OFFICE SKILLS	Card Access Control
System Administration Networking (LAN & WAN)	MS Word, Excel,	Time Clocking System
5	PowerPoint, Outlook	

Bio Data

Sex: Male Nationality: Nigerian LGA: Oyo West State of Origin: Oyo

References

References will be provided upon request.